pressmania.com 2011-12-31

# Privacy Policy | Pressmania

The privacy statement discloses the privacy practices for Pressmania. 

Pressmania agrees to abide by this Privacy Policy with respect to information gathered on web pages hosted by Adlandpro.com and Community.Adlandpro.com 

The terms "we" and "us" refer to Pressmania 

## Our Commitment To Privacy 

Your privacy is important to us. To better protect your privacy we provide this notice explaining our online information collection practices and the choices you can make about the way your information is collected and used. 

## The Information We Collect 

This notice applies to all information collected on the Pressmania web site, or submitted to Pressmania at any time through any web pages which we host. 

## Personally Identifiable Information 

When visiting Pressmania and signing up for or using Pressmania services through a web page hosted by us, you may choose to supply Pressmania with information that identifies you personally. For end-users, this information may include your name and contact information, gender, age group, occupation and industry, and user-comments and opt-in preference; where applicable we collect shipping and billing information, which may, include credit card numbers, and other payment types of information. We also collect behavior patterns, which may include recording frequency of use of our services, which and when items were purchased, at which site and page, and other information related to behavior patterns where applicable. We collect prospect information, which may include name, and contact information of individual(s) you think would be interested in our services. 

## The Way We Use Information 

We use the information you provide about yourself or others to complete the transaction for which it is intended. This may include administering a service such as advertising, search engine submissions, etc., completing an order, shipping a product, or contacting you if you have indicated your permission to do so. We do not share this information with outside parties without your permission. 

When we receive subscribed email addresses or get messages posted on our support forum, we use the return email addresses to reply with the information requested. For subscribed email addresses, we will email with service announcements and updates as requested. Such addresses are not used for any other purpose and are not shared with outside parties. 

For end-users, when supplying name and contact information, shipping information, prospect information, and user-comments to Pressmania, we will use it to answer your questions, ship your products, or provide you with the requested services. 

For prospects, when getting information about you, we will use the information for which it was intended or submitted. You have the right to access and correct information submitted about you, receive the same courteous and professional treatment and services as our end-users and Affiliates. 

Finally, for end-users, and prospects, we never use or share the personally identifiable information provided to us online in ways unrelated to the ones described above without also providing you an opportunity to opt-out or otherwise prohibit such unrelated uses. 

## How You Can Access or Correct Your Information 

For End User, you can access all your personally identifiable information that Pressmania collects online and maintains by logging into your password-protected account at [www.pressmania.com](http://www.pressmania.com/) and selecting to update your "Profile." If you do not currently have an account with us, and have submitted information on our site, you can access and correct the information that we maintain by contacting us. 

To protect your privacy and security, we will also take reasonable steps to verify your identity before granting access or making corrections. 

## How to Contact Us 

Should you have other questions or concerns about our privacy policy, please [contact us](http://www.pressmania.com/contactus.aspx). Content posted to public community areas is publicly available and Pressmania reserves the right to remove any publicly posted content which is objectionable. 

If you have questions or concerns regarding this statement, please [contact us](http://www.pressmania.com/ContactUs.aspx?page=%2fprivacy.aspx).
